

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER & ACADEMIC COORDINATOR

Salinas

Details

5535652078 paulina.lopez1994@gmail.com

Skills

Mongo

English

Microsoft Office

React

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Profile

Self-motivated and enthusiastic Full Stack Web Developer with vast experience in many different fields. Bringing forth a proven track record of achievement and a reputation for positive collaboration. Confident, hard working, and committed to seeing results in whatever position I am in. Reliable and dedicated to finding a place that will benefit from my superior skill set and energetic drive.

Employment History

Academic Coordinator, Colegio Fuentes Brotantes, CDMX

EERRIJARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Responsible for a team of 15 individuals.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.
- · Developed the Website for the Institution
- Currently developing an application for online courses (homework submission, attendance, among others).

English Teacher, Jardín de Niños Willie, CDMX

SEPTEMBER 2016 - AUGUST 2018

- I was working as an English teacher for students ages 2-5.
- I also incorporate sustainability concepts into my lessons.
- CENEVAL Exam

Conservation Society - President, University of Aberdeen , Aberdeen, Scotland

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MAY 2016

- President of the committee.
- Responsible for organizing trips to volunteer in different nature reserves by helping out rangers to manage environmental areas around Scotland.
- Coordinated the committee, established a professional relationship with the rangers, promoted conservation and volunteering awareness in the university
- Organized fundraisers, and social events.

Education

Full Stack Bootcamp, Instituto Tecnológico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey (ITESM), CDMX

MARCH 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

 HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Jquery, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Passport, Mysql, MongoDB, React.

Master of Science - Sustainable Energy, University of Glasgow, Glasgow, Scotland

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Developed different projects that consisted of implementing renewable energies to different urban and rural areas.
- Acquired knowledge in biotechnology, ethics, energy conversion systems.

Bachelor of Science - Conservation Biology 2:1, University of Aberdeen

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Gained experience in teamwork, literature summaries, giving presentations, scientific writing, species identification, fieldwork, and data collection.
- Courses included Sustainability, Environment and Society, Sustainable Resource Management, Statistical Analysis, Conservation in Practice, Behavioral Biology, and Sustainable Aquaculture.